hey everybody welcome to this a2
english listening practice video you can
use this video
to practice your listening and
comprehension
as i speak before we start remember to
subscribe to the channel
click on the bell and follow us on
instagram
you ready so today i'm gonna talk about
childhood i like this topic because
it's fun to look back and remember
things from your childhood
i was born in 1993 so
i grew up in the late 90s and early
2000s
if you were born in a different decade
then you probably had a different type
of childhood than i did
our childhood depends a lot on the time
period that we grew up in
it also depends a lot on the place in
which we grew up
let's talk about that first i grew up in
the suburbs of southern california
which you've probably seen featured in
some american movies
the suburbs are areas around a city
where there are more houses
and fewer businesses there are
residential areas
growing up in the suburbs kids spend a
lot of time
playing outside with their neighbors
during my childhood
i played outside with my neighbors for
hours
on end it's common to play in the
streets
on front lawns or in parks or nature
places
starting from a young age my neighbors
and i
would invent games and use our
imagination
to have fun i also remember playing a
lot of sports
building tree houses and even collecting
bugs
when i was a young child the world was
such a big
and exciting place for me everything was
an adventure however
around the same time i was growing up
video games
and the internet started becoming really
popular
so as each year went by i started
spending more time
indoors playing xbox surfing the web
etc i slowly forgot about all my outside
adventures
nowadays children have much more
technology
than i had when i was young they can
access
all the fun and entertainment they want
in seconds
in most children today probably can't
imagine
what childhood was like before all this
technology
they might imagine it to be lame and
boring
but honestly i think i had more fun
before i started using the internet
regularly i'm really glad that i was
able to experience that
classic american childhood for some
years
before the internet took over how about
you
did you use the internet when you were a
kid another
important part of childhood is family
growing up my household included my mom
my dad my older sister and me
my family situation was pretty standard
my dad worked a full-time job and my mom
worked part-time
so she had more time to spend with me
and my sister
of course i had a lot of fights with my
sister as most siblings do
but we always loved each other did you
fight with your siblings when you were a
kid
so one tradition that my family had
was that we would eat dinner at 6 30 p.m
every day i remember that sometimes
my mother would ring a little bell to
tell us
that dinner was ready this was the
dinner bell
it was great being able to eat that meal
together with my family
every evening it gave us the opportunity
to spend time together
and talk about our day we never watched
tv
when we were eating dinner nowadays it's
less common for american families to eat
dinner together
okay one last thing about childhood that
i wanted to talk about
is cartoons i loved watching cartoons
when i was young
every saturday morning i would wake up
at around 6
50 because all the new episodes of my
favorite cartoons
would start at 7 a.m and on weekdays
there would be new episodes at night too
some of my favorite cartoons were hey
arnold
rocket power and yugioh i really miss
those shows
alright that's all for today leave a
comment
and tell me about your favorite memory
from your childhood
and remember to subscribe to the channel
click on the bell
and follow us on instagram for more
english tips and lessons
i'll see you next time